

PROFILE

A Degree of Bachelor of Science in Electrical Engineering with over 9 years' experience. With a knowledge relating to project management, quantity surveying acquired through practical experience in engineering, construction and consultancy company. A background and experience in supervision/monitoring of construction activities in Electrical and Instrumentation, and in preparation of interim payment applications, cost estimation.

SKILLS

- Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, PowerPoint)
- AutoCad
- Estimation
- Adaptability
- · Willingness to learn
- Multitasking

PERSONAL INFORMATION

NATIONALITY: Filipino

DATE OF BIRTH: December 01,1990

MARITAL STATUS: Single

EDUCATION

Tertiary

Bachelor of Science in Electrical Engineering

Polytechnic University of the Philippines Sta. Mesa, Manila 2007-2012

CHARACTER REFERENCE

Available upon request.

NERISSA TAPICAN DUMDUM

MOBILE: +971547084713 EMAIL: neridumdum01@gmail.com

ADDRESS: 701 Al Hilal Bank Building, Merashid, Fujairah, UAE

WORK EXPERIENCE

QUANTITY SURVEYOR / COST SUPERVISOR (CLAIMS) SK ECOPLANT (Sep. 09, 2021 – present) Fujairah, UAE

Project: ADNOC – M Project (Crude Oil Storage Facility)Duties And Responsibilities:

- Work closely with Project Control Manager, Contracts Manager and Planning Manager on any site related activities and issues.
- Prepare and coordinate periodic reports and special management updates.
- Conducts or assists in performance measurement and associated cost trending.
- Review drawings and documents received from clients and prepare bill of materials and quantities.

QUANTITY SURVEYOR

Dome DZ General Contracting LLC (June 2019 – July 2021)
Abu Dhabi, UAE

Project: ADNOC – Crude Flexibility (CF) Project Duties And Responsibilities:

- Review drawings and documents received from clients and prepare bill of materials and quantities for use with interim of final payment applications, variations, progress claims.
- Visit site and undertake any physical site measurements as may be required
- Track changes to the design and/ construction works.
- Verify and discuss with Planning Engineers to make quantities alignment.
- Draft invoices for client's review and approval and discuss any issues.
- Maintain project documents such as drawings and specifications in an organized manner.

QUANTITY SURVEYOR

Dome DZ General Contracting LLC (July 2017 – March 2018) Abu Dhabi, UAE

Project: EGA – Al Taweelah Alumina Refinery Duties And Responsibilities:

- Review drawings and documents received from clients and prepare bill of materials and quantities.
- Track changes to the design and/ construction works.
- Reconciliation of Bill of Quantities.
- Draft invoices for client's review and approval and follow up draft invoices to the client's QS and discuss any issues.

Electrical Engineer

ArchEn Technologies, Inc, subsidiary of San Miguel
Corporation) (Aug 2014 – Feb-2017)
Mandaluyong City, Philippines
Project: Boracay International Airport Project; 60TPH Feedmills
Plant; Poultry Dressing Plant

Duties And Responsibilities:

- Prepare conceptual designs of assigned task as per instructions and guidelines set by Strategic Project Management Group Head.
- Provide support and guidance on needed coordination to the members of the project review group regarding project inquiries and plant visits necessary to assess properly, facilitating evaluation process.
- Prepare and coordinate periodic reports and special management updates.
- Prepare terms of reference, bid documents, technical specifications.
- Evaluate and prepare technical report from submitted bid documents.
- Prepare bill of quantities and cost estimate from handled projects.
- Assist the Project Manager in the conduct of coordination meeting and the pre-bid

Project Engineer

Voltage Electrical Contractor Corporation (Oct 2012 – July 2014)

Project: Alphaland Makati Place; Landmark Trinoma Expansion; MRT Depot

Duties And Responsibilities:

- Work force supervision and implementation of detailed plan as per designer and owner's approval.
- Inspect electrical & auxiliary layout based to the project standards/speculations.
- Coordinate with other trades concerning all aspect of project implementation.
- Estimate and prepare cost for variation order.
- Reconciliation of Bill of quantities.
- Prepare weekly and monthly report for project updates.
- Prepare invoices for client's review and approval.